The Compact command-line tool provides a set of utilities for Compact smart contract development

Usage: compact [OPTIONS] <COMMAND>

Commands:
  check    Check for updates with the remote server [aliases: ch]
  update   Update to the latest or a specific version of the Compact toolchain [aliases: u, up]
  format   Format compact files [aliases: f, fmt]
  fixup    Apply fixup transformations to compact files [aliases: fx, fix]
  list     List available compact versions [aliases: l]
  clean    Remove all compact versions [aliases: cl]
  self     Commands for managing the compact tool itself [aliases: s]
  compile  Call the compiler [aliases: c]
  help     Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)

Options:
      --directory <DIRECTORY>
          Set the compact artifact directory
          
          By default this will be `$HOME/.compact`. The directory will be created
          if it does not exist. This can also be configured via an environment
          variable.
          
          [env: COMPACT_DIRECTORY=]
          [default: /root/.compact]

  -h, --help
          Print help (see a summary with '-h')

  -V, --version
          Print version
